I made the stupidest, most rookie
mistake you could possibly make, and in
the past 2 days, I've lost $10,000. This
is absolutely ridiculous.
I'm going to be telling you exactly what
mistakes I made, why I made them, and
how you can avoid making the same
mistakes. And of course, I'm going to
get into the Bitcoin analysis later in
this video and talk about exactly what I
think is going to happen as the Bitcoin
price currently is in freefall. So, make
sure to like the video, subscribe to the
channel, click the bell for
notifications
cuz we're bringing you the juiciest
crypto videos here on YouTube. All
right, y'all. I lost $10,000, and here's
why. It all comes down to my trading
psychology, greed, FOMO, and revenge
trading. And I just want to highlight
the fact that I consider myself
a more seasoned trader. I've been doing
this for many years now, and even now,
it's possible for me to not stick to my
rules, not stick to my strategy, and
basically make mistakes that have cost
me
five figures. That That's That's a
pretty hard pill to swallow. Now, let me
kind of paint a picture as to why I
started to make these series of bad
decisions.
It basically For the past few months,
I've been swing trading Bitcoin. I've
been swing trading Bitcoin. I have
locked in a
a short trade here of, you know,
$65,000.
And you know, this was over the course
of a few months as Bitcoin is getting a
big move to the downside to the bottom
of the range, and then I flipped long.
All right, on the 25th of June, I'm
flipping long. I'm opening up long
positions. I'm telling the community,
"Hey, I'm opening up a long trade from
here."
And that's exactly what I did. I ended
up opening two big long positions. All
right, one was from the setup we gave on
the 25th. The other one was from the
setup that was given later from $62,000.
And I'm positioned pretty heftily at
this point. I'm positioned close to a
million dollars in long trades.
And I'm feeling bullish as we're
approaching
the $67,000 level. Why am I feeling
bullish? Well, it's because I understand
if we flip 67 into support, we're going
to get sucked up to $74,000. Now, the
way I trade, guys, is I take a profit
and then I let the runner run, all
right? At the very worst-case scenario,
this trade here has made me $20,000.
If we dump from here, worst case, I get
stopped out around my entry and I've
made five figures. But, if we pump,
then, you know, hey, I'm I'm going to be
making quite a lot of money on move up
to potentially $74,000.
And so, right now, as I'm looking at the
chart
and we're at this level, I'm thinking to
myself, if we flip this into support,
I'm going to be making a lot of money.
Now, here's where the mistake come comes
in. When I went live and I noticed we
were at resistance, I said to myself,
I'm going to take some profit here. Let
me lock in more than $35,000 realized
profit. Let me get this like 40
$45,000. So, I tried to take a partial
profit and instead, I accidentally
closed this entire position live. Now,
when I did that, you can see here, now
there's only one position open, it
really messed with my psychology because
one of the things that helps me in my
trading psychology is knowing that I'm
in a trade, right? Knowing that I am
long in case the price pumps, I know
that I'm long. And at the very worst,
I'm going to be making $60,000 if price
comes all the way down and stops down at
my entry. But, at the very best, I could
be making six figures on these trades.
Now that I'm out of the trade, it's a
massive hit to my psychology. Because I
was bullish, because I was expecting
higher, I'm like, "Oh man, I can't
believe I closed out of this massive It
was a It was like a $600,000 long trade
when I could have kept it open and I
could have made more money."
And so, this really messed with me. And
so, the following day, I opened up a
long trade
that was actually not a bad trade to
take.
But, I didn't approach it the way I
should have.
Every trade that you take needs to have
three things. Every single trade you
take needs to have a reason for the
entry,
a place to get out if it goes against
you, and a place to get out if it goes
for you. Now, the problem I made with
taking this series of trades after
accidentally closing my long was I had
two of the three things correct, all
right? I had a valid reason to take a
trade, I had a valid risk,
but I didn't have
a valid take profit.
All right? Instead, what I did was I
took a long trade from here.
I ended up taking two long trades from
here,
and both of these trades, guys, all
right?
Both of these trades could have been
winners.
All right? They could have been winners.
They could have been valid scalp
entries. We had valid scalp confirmation
for all these. I held them all into
profit at least over a thousand dollars
the profit for each trade, but what I
didn't do is I didn't take profit. Why?
Because instead of logically coming to
the chart and saying this is a scalp
trade with a clear stop loss and target,
I said, "I'm going to take this trade
and I'm going to hold it so that if we
come back up here, now I can feel like I
didn't close that trade. Now I can feel
like I'm back in the move, and I can
finally take that ride up to $74,000."
And so, all three of these trades that
you see here, I had the opportunity to
close them in massive profit. I had the
opportunity to close this $4,000 loss
in like over $5,000 profit.
That's crazy.
I even used looser stop losses because I
took a scalp trade and I used a swing
trade-ish stop loss,
didn't take profit.
It's because of the fear It's because
not the fear, it's because the greed.
It's because the revenge trading. And
now, I have to deal with this. I've
given back $11,000 of my profits
because I didn't stick to my strategy
and I didn't stick to my rules. And it
sucks, but it is what it is. And again,
I just want to reiterate and remind
everybody that, you know, it doesn't
matter how long you've been doing this,
there are things If your psychology is
off, you can make those stupid
decisions. You can turn trading into
gambling, which I absolutely did for
these three losses. And what could have
been me making money by taking valid
scalp trades turns into me giving back
my hard-earned profits
that basically for the last month, like,
you know, it took me 20 days to make
that 57K.
All right. So, guys, make sure to stick
to your rules. Make sure to stick to
your strategy. If you find yourself not
doing so, close the damn computer and
stop taking trades.
So, now let's talk about what Bitcoin is
doing now as we're coming back down to
the bottom of this channel. What do I
think is going to happen next for
Bitcoin? Now, just a quick reminder,
guys, if you want to trade Bitcoin and
altcoins, I'm trading on Antarctic
decentralized exchange, lowest fees in
the game. Same with KCS, guys. KCS
literally has the lowest fees in the
game, and right now I'm working with
BitBase. BitBase is giving $500 a week
to basically people who sign up using my
link. Not only do you get VIP level 7
fees on BitBase, but every single week
in my live streams we're giving away
$500 courtesy of BitBase. All right.
Also, if you want to join the Casper
Crew to get the juicy trade setups in
the moment, you can go to
JasonCasperTrading.com. Now,
the Bitcoin price has come up and has
rejected from the macro POC of the
range. Okay, the macro POC of the range,
and we are coming down to support area
number one.
Support area number one, of course, is
this POC that we have right here around
$64,000.
If the price right now can reclaim this
POC and close the daily candle above,
well, we very well may just continue to
trade this sideways channel, and we very
well may
just come back up and and hit that
$74,000
level, all right? This is one
possibility and it looks like right now
we are struggling with this POC. We're
below it, we're trying to reclaim it. If
we cannot reclaim the POC, the next
place to look for the long is going to
be to take all of this liquidity and
come down to the value area low of the
range around $60,000.
This is where we very well may make our
shoulder, our head, our shoulder, and
then get a move back up toward the top
of the range, toward the $70,000 zone.
Why am I still bullish even if
we're getting this move all the way
down? The reason why I'd still be
bullish here is because the context is
the higher term time frames have bullish
divergences confirmed, right? The 2-week
time frame has a confirmed bullish
divergence. The I'm sorry, the weekly
has that. The 2-week very well may
confirm a bullish divergence just in 9
days and then of course the daily time
frame has just gotten a money flow cross
right here on Market Cipher B. And when
you get a money flow cross after a
bullish divergence, that next trigger
wave you get at the higher low is a very
powerful move. Typically continues that
trend to the upside.
So, this is kind of what I would be
looking for if we came down to this
area. Of course, if we hold 64K, then we
might just bounce from this green
trendline. If we lose 64K, highest
probability is coming down to around the
$60,000 zone. Now, I'm not saying we're
guaranteed to bounce from there. I'm
saying that is the next place I am
currently looking for
a long trade. And so right now, I'm
looking at the daily close. It's a
Friday, we're heading into the weekend.
Can we close the weekly candle above 64K
in the next few days?
If we can, that's kind of bullish. If
not, let's expect some of this liquidity
to get taken. Let's look for some
bullish divergences and some trigger
waves on the daily down around 60K.
That's where I would be looking for my
next juicy
long trade.
All right, guys. That's it for today's
video. God bless everybody in the name
of Jesus, Yeshua the Messiah. I pray you
and your family are super blessed.
And I'll see everybody in the next
video. Peace.